hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
Evening Shower
Hey.
Are you all right?
Why?
Your face looks terrible!
Did you get enough sleep over the weekend?
Yeah.
You look really out of it to me.
That’s not true.
You need to get yourself cleaned up for the event.
I know.
Are you still brooding over it?
Your break-up?
No way.
Well, it’s fine then.
Actually,
Party Meeting Room
Machida
Marriage
Consulting
I really don’t have any regrets about getting dumped.
Koshiro, have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
No.
I’m not really very clever.
You don’t look that way.
...and then I fell down.
Odagiri!
Yes?
...but usually I’m very careful.
So, are you going to attend today’s after-party?
The chief said he’ll treat us.
Really? Yes!
Of course I’m in!
I already have plans, so I can’t go.
Plans?
A movie. I’m just watching a movie.
Are you going with Nanoka?
What’s your point?
I can’t do anything about it. She made me promise to go with her.
I’d love to go with you!
Shut up! Just go out for drinks with the chief!
Hey, Koshiro.
The other day, after we had a meeting here, didn’t you pick up a high school girl?
Was that...?
Picking up?!
A high school girl?!
M-M-Moron! I-I didn’t!
She was...
That was Nanoka, wasn’t it?
If you knew she was your sister, why didn’t you just say so?
Odagiri, help me carry these.
Yes.
What did you mean when you said he, “picked up Nanoka”?
I wonder...
I don’t really get it either.
Why? Why?
Don’t stare at me like it’s that unusual.
But I’m curious!
You had a beard this morning!
We have to look clean for our events, or we’ll get in trouble.
Look clean?
Is it weird?
You look cool!
But it looks painful!
What are you talking about?
Hey, this movie is...
Don’t get so close to me!
Thank you very much.
You’re welcome.
Why are you spacing out?
No reason.
Give me your student ID.
Oh, right.
What’s wrong?
I’ll go buy the tickets.
What was he thinking, making you come home all alone at this hour?
He said, “It doesn’t matter; just go home first”.
That guy is hopeless.
He went off somewhere as soon as the movie ended.
Where did that bum go?
I don’t know. He didn’t say anything.
Hey.
Your uniform’s going to get wrinkled.
I don’t care.
So?
About earlier.
That was my younger sister.
I don’t think I ever told you, but...
I have a younger sister, and we were living separately.
You know my parents are divorced, right?
She’s been with my mom the whole time.
We started living together this spring because her high school is nearby.
That’s it?
Is that really all?
Yeah.
What?
You said you had something to tell me, so I was wondering what it could be.
It’s not a laughing matter!
I didn’t want you to think I started going after high school girls since getting dumped.
I was worried for nothing.
It’s just so like you, to be worried about appearances while dating high school girls.
Well, I’m sorry.
I’ll never come see you again.
Dinner?
Have you eaten yet?
Suddenly, a foolish thought passed through my mind.
“That’s right; it’s been three months since the last time I had sex”.
Go on! You can drink, right?
That’s not true.
It is! You can drink way more than I can!
I don’t think so.
Isn’t it good?
This place is a hidden gem.
Yeah.
I come here often by myself.
What are you saying, stupid?
I’m not stupid. I’m serious.
I don’t believe you!
There’s no way I’d joke about that!
What about Sachiko?
She’s just a friend.
Liar!
I’m serious!
You’re the only person...
Hey...
How’s work been lately?
Why?
You used to always tell me that you wanted to quit.
You still remember?
Who could forget, after listening to you complain so much?
Going by your half-hearted replies, I thought you weren’t listening.
That’s not true.
So, how’s your job?
The same as always, I guess.
I see.
And you?
Did you have an event today?
Yeah.
Or did you shave your beard because your high school girlfriend told you to?
I told you, she’s...
What is it?
Nothing.
What?
I was wondering if any taxis would come this way.
If you go a little further you’ll reach the main street.
It’ll be easier to find one there.
I’m moving next month.
I’m quitting my job, too.
Although, that’ll happen a bit later.
I see.
To tell you the truth, my boyfriend is coming over.
Yeah.
What?
He’s a very nice person.
I see.
Best of luck to you, Koshiro.
Really.
Good night.
“What would you like to do tonight?”
I’m really glad I didn’t ask her anything stupid like that.
I’m really, really glad.
Don’t stay up too late!
Yes.
I wasn’t going out with her just for the sex.
Koshiro, have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
Even if I had been, I don’t think that’s so wrong.
Is it that big of a deal to fall in love with someone?
Is true love something to be really proud of?
What kind of feeling is “true love”, anyway?
That idiot!
Onii-chan?
Sorry!
Good morning.
I’m sorry about last night,
for suddenly barging in on you.
I’ll be careful next time.
The movie—
let’s go see another one.
But you have to come home with me next time.
What?
Nothing.
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
Ya... umm... well....
Next episode:
Distant Thunder
Every man has trash that he doesn't want other people to find. Nanoka was being nice trying to clean it up.
Koshiro's face twitches, because he can't get mad at her.
I’m sorry I sniffed them. I’m sorry I sniffed them.
I’m sorry I sniffed them!
Innocent
Innocent?!
Like hell!
Innocent
Like Hell
I’m so sorry.