hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
Distant Thunder
Hey, Daddy, will there be a panda? A panda?
Hey, Dad, did you bring the camera?
I sure did!
What? A panda?
Okay, I’ll be back soon.
Unbelievable.
You’re still here?
Onii-chan, if you have nothing else to do, can you at least help by cleaning the bathroom?
Did she notice?
It was only for an instant.
There’s no way.
There’s no way...
Onii-chan.
What should we have for
lunch? Are cold noodles okay?
Dad still hasn’t come back from his haircut.
Let’s just go ahead and eat—
You went into my room, didn’t you?
Yeah.
Tomorrow is garbage day, so I just...
I’ve told you before, haven’t I?
Don’t go in there without my permission.
But...
All I did was empty your trash can.
I didn’t touch anything else—
That’s not the problem!
I can take care of my own trash!
You wouldn’t like it if I went into your room without asking, right?
I’m sorry.
You’re right.
Idiot! You’re so inconsiderate.
Don’t say that.
I was just trying to do something nice.
Nobody asked you to!
Don’t make me repeat myself again.
What was that?
An insinuation?
No. It’s impossible.
It was just for an instant.
There’s no way she could have noticed.
But...
That’s suspicious.
Really?
Definitely suspicious. Why would he get so angry just because you went into his room?
Maybe there was something he really didn’t want you to see.
Ah, I know!
What? What?
A present.
He made himself seem like a major jerk,
but tomorrow he’ll suddenly transform into a nice big brother.
Ah! So that’s his plan!
Nanoka, it’s your birthday tomorrow, right?
What? No way! He’d never do that.
Your brother might be more simple minded than you think.
Marriage
Consulting
Bamboo? Why does it have to be bamboo?
It’s the “Tanabata Matchmaking Party”.
We need to set a romantic atmosphere for young girls!
Young girls?
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the “Star Festival Matchmaking Party”
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Wh-What are you doing?!
By the way, he looks pretty ominous over there.
Look at the way he’s decorating that bamboo without complaining.
I want to
have a
younger
sister.
Odagiri
Wh-What are you doing?!
I’m telling you, there’s nothing good about having a younger sister.
A guy who fights over the TV channels with his cute younger sister could never understand my feelings!
Man, it’s like a sauna out here.
Going outside is the worst.
Do you want to go for a drink?
Sure! I was just about to ask you.
Is it all right not to call home?
Ever since Nanoka-chan started living with you,
you always call home whenever you’re going to be late, right?
No, I haven’t.
There’s no use hiding it.
Shut up and wipe your mouth.
I don’t care about that brat.
She’s the one who suddenly invaded my life.
She’s not worth the trouble.
I really don’t give a damn about her.
Onii-chan?
Don’t come over here!
The broken pieces are dangerous.
That’s... my rice bowl.
That was my favorite bowl! What are you going to do?
I won’t be able to eat my rice tomorrow.
Hey, Onii-chan...
Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
I’m leaving early tomorrow, so I won’t need a lunch.
Why won’t I say it?
“I’m sorry I sniffed your bra”.
“I’m sorry it made me excited”.
No.
What good would saying that do?
She might be wearing that bra right now, without knowing what I did.
That time...
Hey, Koshiro left really early today, too.
Does he know that today’s your birthday?
It doesn’t matter.
I don’t need a big brother.
"I don't need
a big brother".
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother".
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother".
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother".
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother".
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother".
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother".
The father's
free translation.
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad".
Zenzo
The best hospitality of this inn is the small mosquito.
This is a Haiku written by Bashou.
Ah, I know!
What? What?
A present.
He made himself seem like a major jerk,
but tomorrow he’ll suddenly transform into a nice big brother.
Ah! So that’s his plan!
Nanoka, it’s your birthday tomorrow, right?
I want to
have a
younger
sister.
Odagiri
Your father called.
Nanoka-chan left without taking an umbrella, so he wants you to wait for her at the station.
Why me?
He can’t leave because he’s preparing for her birthday party.
Birthday party?
This is why you...
Hey, Onii-chan...
Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
You should go.
You can leave early—
I just don’t get it.
This is my chance! It’s her birthday!
It’s an opportunity for me to fix everything!
I’ll tell her “Happy birthday!” or “I’m sorry I forgot about it!”
Then we’ll have a big celebration, and I’ll try to flatter her as much as I can.
She’s so simple-minded, she’ll be overjoyed and maybe even cry if I just buy her some flowers.
This way I can wash away my guilt!
Ticket Gate to Manase
I can wash away...
I can...
I’m sorry.
No! No, it’s no good! Damn it!
There’s nothing I can do! I’m the worst!
God, I’m the worst!
No, no, no, that’s not what I meant!
I just wanted to say I’m sorry for forgetting about your birthday!
It’s nothing more than that.
It’s okay.
It’s fine.
Are you here to pick me up?
N-No, I-I-I was just...
Are those for me?
N-No way, you idiot!
They’re for our Buddha statue!
I’m relieved.
I thought you were angry at me because I saw you naked in the bathroom.
Why would I be angry?
It’s normal to be just in my underwear the whole day with this weather.
What? Seriously?
Yeah.
I see.
I’m sorry, too.
Yeah! You were acting really scary last night!
For your birthday present,
I’ll buy you whatever you want.
Really?
Well, then...
Shop
Yamazato
I was going to do that...
To wash away my sense of guilt.
Why couldn’t I?
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
I’ll say it over and over again!
Autumn Melancholy
Next episode:
My adorable little sister has a boyfriend? I totally misunderstand and put myself in an awkward situation.
I innocently want to have a teenage sister.
Big brother and little sister get into a fight. Koshiro trembles.
Is that a crime?
Is that something to be ashamed of?
Then, as we’re fighting over TV channels, we’ll start to fall in love...
Flog Him
Sentenced to a flogging!