hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
Dew frost
The conference members are basically selected after we do a strict examination.
There really aren’t any suspicious people, so to say...
or any people with problems.
If there are any conflicts between two members,
we’ll take responsibility...
It was a job I just chose to do,
because employment opportunities were limited for a third-class university graduate.
Or so I thought.
Or I was trying to make myself think.
In truth, I wanted to experience people’s happiness,
I wanted to experience people’s sadness.
I wanted to place myself somewhere where people encounter and separate.
If I kept doing that, I thought I’d be able to do the same someday...
From now on, I want you to help me with the house chores more often than before, okay?
I feel kind of bad doing this to you since there’s such a large age difference.
What’s wrong? You don’t seem too happy.
You’re finally going to be a big brother...
Oh, isn’t it almost time?
One more month.
You’re a big brother now, aren’t you, Ko-chan?
Yes! We did it, Koshiro!
Congratulations, it’s a girl.
It was a kind of a happy, yet scary, feeling.
But that was the only time I had that feeling.
I’m home.
What is it?
What do you want?!
Hey, wait...
My, my, what’s going on?
Come on, what’s the matter?
Ugh... Not again.
Now, now, don’t cry, don’t cry.
It’s not my fault!
Here.
Which is it?!
You aren’t bullying her while we’re out, are you?
Nanoka seems to be afraid of you!
Who cares!
You’re so helpless.
It wasn’t me!
That’s not it.
Will you come to the other room?
It’s not that we’re quarreling with each other,
or we got into a big fight or anything.
It’s just...
We thought we should live separately before that happens.
That’s right.
We’re sorry that we have to make you go through some sad times.
We’re really sorry about that.
Even though we’ll be living apart,
it doesn’t mean I’ll stop being your mother,
or that she’s no longer your sister.
We’re still family.
Yeah.
I thought divorces weren’t such peaceful things in my mind as a child, but...
I could tell that mom and dad were trying to separate peacefully for me.
Well, we should get going.
Koshiro, keep an eye on the house for me.
Okay.
Bye now.
Don’t look so sulky forever.
Be more honest with yourself, okay?
Yeah.
You can come any time.
Good work.
What, you’ve been going home early lately.
What?
He must want to see Nanoka-san as soon as possible.
I’m so envious!
No way. He’s not you.
I love you, Onii-chan.
Why is it that I even headed there?
Without even understanding it myself,
I was walking in the town that she grew up in without me knowing.
My!
So you finally came to my house.
How did you know?
Of course I’d know!
It’s you, Koshiro!
I thought you would’ve forgotten my face.
Did you forget my face?
See? Even if we haven’t seen each other for years, that’s how it is between a parent and child.
And?
What’s the matter?
Did something happen?
Why?
You just suddenly came. There must be some reason, isn’t there?
No reason. I just felt like it.
Really?
From when she was a child...
Oh.
She just loves bears.
She really is your younger sister, that kid.
You exchanged dolls, I heard.
Nanoka was talking about it so happily when she came back during summer vacation.
Why did you send her over to our house?
When you took her with you when you got divorced,
why would you suddenly bring her back to dad?
Because she got into a high school near your house.
Are you serious?
I’d feel bad if she had to commute two hours each way every day.
What? What’s the matter?
It’s nothing.
What? Did you come all the way over just to sulk?
What are you doing?
Here, come with me.
What is it?
How many years has it been since I last cut your hair?
I forgot.
You wouldn’t let me cut it much after you became a big brother.
What were you getting all worked up about?
Onii-chan.
What?
She isn’t bothering you?
Saying, Onii-chan, Onii-chan, Onii-chan...
How do you know?
Well, you see...
I wonder what Onii-chan is like?
I want to meet him soon.
I wonder if he’ll help me with studying.
Oh, nothing, nothing at all.
He will help you, I’m sure, with your studies.
Yeah!
She probably really wanted to live with you guys... or just you.
Oh...
So take good care of her, okay?
Zenzo-san is no good when you really need him.
Okay...
What? You’d better make sure you take care of things.
You’re a big brother, aren’t you?
Hey.
What would you do if I made her unhappy?
What?
If I somehow made her unhappy,
what would you do?
If such a thing happened,
I wouldn’t let you get away with it.
Of course.
Weird kid.
You still don’t seem to be very honest with yourself.
Really?
It means you haven’t grown up at all.
You’d better be stronger.
It’s the most difficult phase
at that age.
Why don’t you stay a little longer, since its been a while?
How can I?
I have work tomorrow too.
You have to eat properly.
Okay.
Oh yes. Nanoka’s flavoring is usually a little too strong,
so tell her to be careful.
Yeah, I got it.
And don’t give her too much allowance.
I wouldn’t give her any even if she begged.
And tell her not to stay up too late.
I got it already. I’ll be late for my train.
But...
I know.
I understand.
Thank you, Koshiro.
Okay, bye.
Get along with her, okay?
Yeah.
I’m back.
Welcome home, Onii-chan.
I’m... home.
Want some?
Okay.
You’re not going to cry?
Eh?
No, nothing.
Hey, Onii-chan?
Where did you go today?
Somewhere.
What?
Just for a walk.
To where?
Somewhere.
You should’ve taken me too.
I’m fine with being Onii-chan.
I’m fine with just being close to each other as siblings.
If that’s the role that I was given,
I’ll do what I must.
So...
Don’t you have to get up early tomorrow?
Yeah.
But you too, Onii-chan.
I’ll take a smoke and then go to sleep.
So go to sleep.
Okay.
I’ll do it.
Good night then.
Yeah.
So don’t say that you love me.
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
I’m Nanoka’s father Zenzo, who isn’t any good when I’m needed most.
Next episode:
Wind flower
Koshiro starts keeping distance from Nanoka and begins to act more like her big brother.
So, Nanoka starts trusting Koshiro more. Koshiro is happy.
Unable to stand that inconsiderate part of Makei-san, I resorted to this.
Play out the machine!
Excrete red ball punishment!