hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
Autumn Melancholy
We still have some eggs left,
so all we need is crab meat and mitsuba.
Yesterday I made rice with green peas for dinner, thinking it would be good dish for autumn,
but Onii-chan said it tasted like a school cafeteria lunch.
That’s why I’m going to make crab porridge for dinner tonight.
I’ve never seen it served in a cafeteria.
I’m sure Dad will enjoy it,
and I hope Onii-chan will be impressed...
But he probably won’t be.
I’m trying my best to get along with him,
even though he’s arrogant and mean to me.
I found out he can be nice recently,
but he’s normally so blunt and grumpy.
Kohinata-san.
Miyauchi-kun.
I’ll take those for you.
Oh, thank you.
Even though we’re the executive committee, we have to do the janitorial work.
Yeah.
Doesn’t it suck?
It’s not that bad.
Miyauchi, your class is doing a haunted house, right?
That’s what Tamaki-chan said.
Yeah.
That sounds like fun.
Our class is just doing a simple exhibition.
It’s all been done before.
Did you invite anyone, Miyauchi-kun?
Perhaps a friend?
Not really.
Oh...
I’m planning to invite my brother.
He can’t just take any day off from work, though,
so he may not be able to come to our Annual Culture Festival.
So the rumors about you having a brother complex are true.
What? That’s not true! I don’t have a brother complex!
Reference Material Room
Where’d you hear that?
Nowhere.
Don’t give me that!
I overheard Tamaki talking to her friends.
Well, Tamaki-chan and Futaba-chan were just making fun of me.
Is going to the movies or shopping with my brother that unusual?
It’s true that I like my brother, but...
Don’t let the rumors get to you.
Don’t worry about them.
And... As for me, nothing has changed.
Marriage
Consulting
The feelings of guilt gradually went away over time.
Again I...
I’m not trying to shift the blame or anything,
but recently I keep thinking...
Is it really that weird for me to imagine my little sister when I masturbate?
Little sister, little sister, little sister!
Matchmaking Party Proposal
For People Interested in Dating Outside of Their Age Category
"Boyfriends who are like big brothers, and girlfriends who are like little sisters".
Matchmaking Party Proposal
For People Interested in Dating Outside of Their Age Category
"Boyfriends who are like big brothers, and girlfriends who are like little sisters".
Matchmaking Party Proposal
For People Interested in Dating Outside of Their Age Category
"Boyfriends who are like big brothers, and girlfriends who are like little sisters".
Matchmaking Party Proposal
For People Interested in Dating Outside of Their Age Category
"Boyfriends who are like big brothers, and girlfriends who are like little sisters".
Matchmaking Party Proposal
For People Interested in Dating Outside of Their Age Category
"Boyfriends who are like big brothers, and girlfriends who are like little sisters".
You’re never going to grow up, are you?
Never.
My admiration of little sisters will endure throughout my whole life!
Right, Koshiro-san?
Don’t drag me into your fantasy world.
So you say, but I’m pretty sure I saw you out walking with Nanoka-chan last Sunday.
What did you—?!
It must’ve been wonderful, going on a “date” with your little sister.
I wish I had a cute little brother who would go out with me.
Oh, really?
But isn’t it kind of pathetic for her to be going on a “date” with her brother?
Do you know if she has a boyfriend?
She’s so childish there’s no way she would.
Maybe you’re the only one who thinks that.
A boyfriend...
“Onii-chan”...
She won’t cling on to me for much longer.
Oh, really?
Yeah. That’s why my brother’s last name is Saeki, but mine is Kohinata.
Isn’t that weird? We have different last names, even though we’re siblings.
Do you have any siblings, Miyauchi-kun?
I have an older sister.
An older sister? That’s nice.
How much older is she?
Just two years.
Oh, so she’s still in high school?
It’s nice that your ages are so close.
My brother and I are twelve years apart,
and he’s always in a bad mood.
Onii-chan!
This is my brother.
Good evening. I’m Miyauchi, a first year in class 4.
He walked me home because we had to stay late for the Culture Festival preparations.
Well, I’ll see you later.
Okay, thanks.
Onii-chan, it was rude of you to not even say hello.
Ouch!
Onii-chan, that hurts! You’re hurting me!
Hey! Onii-chan! What’s your problem?
“Preparing for the Culture Festival”, my ass!
It’s ten years too early for you to be going out with a guy!
Until you’re old enough to take responsibility for yourself,
I won’t allow it!
What are you talking about?!
Miyauchi-kun was just being kind and walking me home!
Just being kind?! Are you completely obtuse?!
You don’t know what ulterior motives he has!
Use your brain a little more!
You’re the only one who thinks such disgusting thoughts!
Idiot! You have to be more careful!
I am careful!
You are not!
Why do you act like you know everything—
Because you’re so cute!
No. That’s not actually my opinion.
I’m just... I mean, objectively speaking.
As your older brother, it’s only natural for me to be worried about you.
This is more dad’s opinion than mine; actually, it’s our opinion as a family.
Hey, what’s going on?
If you keep shouting, you’re going to bother the neighbors.
H-Hey, N-N-Nanoka?
Wh-wh-what happened?
Hell if I know!
Please    knock
Nanoka
I was so surprised.
Jeez. What’s wrong with him?
You two are siblings. Try to get along better!
Shut up! I didn’t ask to be a brother!
Koshiro!
Nanoka already left.
I see.
Here.
That certainly seemed a bit staged.
But I don’t care.
Onii-chan was really mean last night.
“Cute”... He said.
How weird.
No way! A molester?
Oh god, no! No! No! It was so gross!
Man, that sucks! Didn’t your brother protect you?
It’s not like I’m always with him!
First it was guilt, and now it’s jealousy?
I’m home.
Welcome home.
Dinner is ready.
Okay.
Isn’t Onii-chan late?
Is he?
I guess not.
He usually comes back late.
That’s right, I’m angry at him.
Why does he always talk down to me?
Because you’re so cute!
I was just surprised.
I never imagined I’d hear those words from my brother.
That’s all.
Good night.
Should I make up with him tomorrow?
What? He left before me?
Ouch!
Good morning.
Why? Stingy! Meanie!
He couldn’t have waited for me just a little?
Kohinata-san.
Miyauchi-kun.
The festival tickets for my class are ready.
Okay, thanks.
You should come with your brother.
Year 1 - Class 4 Haunted House
Couple Ticket
I’ll never invite him anywhere!
Your proposal for the next event sounds very good.
Yeah.
I looked over the data you put together, and it’s very convincing.
I’m sure the boss will agree.
Yeah.
You seem depressed!
Let’s go together this morning.
No, thanks. I’ll go alone.
You know what?
Don’t avoid me forever just because you’re holding a grudge.
Aren’t you the one who’s avoiding me?
You came home late yesterday, too.
Not that I care about that.
Listen.
Just because you’re older than I am doesn’t mean you should act so bossy.
Why do you have to talk to me like you’re better than I am?
I... Don’t like you at all!
It’s fine that you don’t like me.
I think I was a little too hard on you the other day.
I’m sorry.
I won’t tell you not to go out with guys any more,
but don’t come home so late or lie to me.
I didn’t lie to you!
I know.
I’m saying, don’t do it in the future.
I don’t want you to make us worry about you. That’s all.
I wonder if he really worries about me.
Hey, we missed the train because of you.
It was because of your lecture.
If something bad happens to you, your guardians are the ones who get blamed.
Don’t treat me like a kid.
You are a kid.
No, I’m not!
Excuse me.
Sorry.
The doors are closing. Please stand clear.
I hope you stay a child,
just as you are now.
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
I’m so sorry.
Next episode:
First Storm
I couldn’t touch her because she was always with her big boyfriend.
Nanoka gets a love letter. Koshiro is extremely worried...
but pretends he's not affected, and gives her some mature advice. Koshiro walks with heavy feet.
She was alone today, so I tried to console her...
And I touched her!
Go to hell!