hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
First Storm
Why?
Why were my cheeks so flushed?
Why was my heart beating so fast?
My face still feels hot.
I feel strange.
This is really annoying!
The guys in class 4 are slacking on the culture festival preparations!
They’re having a “beauty contest” and ranking all the first-year girls, instead.
I think those jerks should take a good look in the mirror first!
That sounds like fun!
We should rank the boys by their looks, too!
Nanoka!
What are you thinking about?
Which guys are at the top of your list?
I don’t really know the boys in the other classes.
How about Miyauchi?
I heard you went home with him the other day!
When did you get so close to him?
Yeah, when?
I’m not!
We just stayed late to finish some executive committee work!
The way you’re defending yourself just makes me more suspicious.
That’s not it!
I’m sorry. It must be embarrassing for you.
Everyone... Everyone’s just joking around.
Its fine. I don’t really mind.
Hey... Can you read this later?
This?
It’s kind of like a love letter.
But we only talked for the first time just the other day!
This is so sudden...
It’s not from me.
It’s from this guy named Asano in my class.
Oh, really.
I see. I was just...
I didn’t mean to make it sound like I don’t like you, Miyauchi-kun.
How can I say this right? Um...
Please read it.
Well, he doesn’t look like a bad person.
I think he’s nice, but he is pretty plain looking...
Hey, Nanoka, tell us what you think!
Hey, let’s stop spying on him.
You say that, but I know you’re curious, too.
Why don’t you go talk to him?
He’s probably just playing a joke on me.
I’m sure that’s not true.
Excuse me...
Why did you run away? That was a good chance to talk to him!
There’s always tomorrow.
You should walk around the festival with him.
But...
Try going out with him once, and decide if you want to go out with him for real later.
But, but what do you do when you “go out” with someone?
Well, you can do a whole bunch of things!
Like walk home together, visit his house, or take a walk in the park.
A park?
Maybe if you get a boyfriend, you’ll be able to grow out of your brother complex.
I don’t have a brother complex!
What’s wrong?
Um... Tomorrow is my school’s culture festival...
You’re welcome to come if you want to.
Sorry, I have to work.
What is it?
You don’t look too happy.
No, I’m fine.
Onii-chan, promise me you won’t get mad.
Dear Nanoka Kohinata,
I know receiving a letter
like this might surprise you.
I've been interested in you
since the first day of school.
He doesn’t seem like a bad person, but the letter is written so casually.
I thought he might just be playing a joke on me.
I shouldn’t go on a date with someone I’ve never talked to before, right?
I don’t really know him very well.
That’s why he wants to spend time with you, to get to know you.
Futaba-chan said the same thing.
Anyway, don’t show me letters like this.
Even if the letter was written casually, he might be serious.
I don’t think you should show important letters like this to anyone.
I was just trying to get your advice
because I don’t know what to do!
I said, if you don’t think he’s a bad guy,
try going out with him once.
If you get along well, then you can continue going out.
Maybe it’ll work out.
You don’t mind?
Why are you asking me that?
Because you got really mad the other day when Miyauchi-kun simply walked me home.
I’m sorry about that. I won’t treat you like a little kid anymore.
Do whatever you want.
I see. I guess you’re right.
It’s my own problem. I should make my own decision.
Thanks for listening.
He’s right.
This really has nothing to do with you, Onii-chan.
I’m sorry, but I can’t really think about seeing anyone right now.
Don’t take it so seriously. I was just hoping we could have a fun time together today.
But...
Is there someone else you like?
No, not at all!
Don’t worry about it. I don’t mind.
I’m actually really busy with my class’s haunted house.
I have to go back now!
I guess I’ve made you feel uncomfortable. I’m sorry.
I’m the one who needs to apologize.
Do whatever you want.
Huh?
That’s weird...
Why am I crying?
Machida
Marriage
Consulting
Special Event
Matchmaking Party
Planning Overview
A picture of my brother?
Don’t you have one?
He didn’t come to the culture festival, after all.
I want to see what your famous prince of a brother looks like at least once.
No. He’s not good looking at all.
He has a thick beard, and he even smells like an old man.
Is he stinky? What does he smell like?
He smells weird?
Here, put this in the laundry.
Does it smell that bad?
It doesn’t really stink, but...
They’re three runs down, and it’s the bottom of the ninth with two outs.
Runners are on first and third base.
Yoshimura’s up to bat.
Today, he’s been up to bat four times and has hit two singles.
If he hits a home run now, the score will be tied.
It’s a big hit heading for right field! Foul!
A nice hit, but it didn’t go straight.
Ueda is warming up in the bullpen,
but the coach, Ohmori, hasn’t signaled yet.
The second pitch...
A hit!
It’s a line drive straight down the field!
The runner on third is heading home! Safe!
The runner on first rounds third base and is heading for home!
Onii-chan...
Will you help me with my homework?
No. Too much work.
Why?
I don’t remember any high school math.
Stop staring at me!
I’m not staring.
You’re distracting me.
For that one, just use the formula.
I knew that!
That’s not very cute.
Hey, what about this one?
Look over it carefully.
Which part?
You messed up on the first calculation.
Oh. I see. I do that a lot.
No way! The homework was due today?
Nanoka!
All right.
I won’t finish in time! The teacher’s coming soon!
If Futaba-chan and the others saw Onii-chan, what would they say?
I guess he isn’t really that cool.
See ya.
Leaving so soon?
Is your sister waiting for you at home with a nice dinner?
Yeah.
He doesn’t get agitated any more when I mention her.
Onii-chan always has a sullen look. I never know what he’s thinking.
Asajigaoka Station
He’s mean and gets angry quickly,
but on the other hand, sometimes he’s nice.
And it surprises me.
Hey! Be careful!
Here.
I’m sorry.
Hey, so...
How’d it go with the guy who wrote you that letter?
Did you have fun at the culture festival?
If something is bothering you,
feel free to talk to me.
Oh, that?
Weren’t you worried because you didn’t know how to handle a relationship with him?
I turned him down.
Oh, you did?
Yeah.
What? Were you worried about me?
Not really.
You were, admit it!
I said I wasn’t!
Besides, it’s 10 years too early for you to have a boyfriend.
You said you’d stop treating me like a kid.
What kind of adult would swing a grocery bag around like that?
Were you following me the whole way?
Why the hell would I do that?
I just saw you on top of the hill over there!
How weird! You were spying on me and laughing at me!
I wasn’t laughing at you.
It’s fine for you to swing the bag around. That’s just like you, Nanoka.
You just called me Nanoka for the first time.
R-Really?
Yes! You always call me, “you” so arrogantly!
I’m not trying to be arrogant.
You always surprise me like this.
It isn’t fair.
I don’t know what you’re saying.
I...
I like you, Onii-chan.
What are you saying?!
I didn’t mean it like that!
Mean it like what?!
You’re weird, blushing like that! So weird!
It’s not like that!
I’ll see you at home.
What are you...
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
I don’t think I have a brother complex.
Next episode:
Dew frost
Koshiro goes to see his mother... to reconcile his feelings toward his little sister.
But, Koshiro can't get rid of that feeling.
I just asked him for advice when I got a love letter from this guy.
Do I really have a brother complex?
Brother Complex
Sentenced to a brother complex!
??
W-What’s going on?