hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
Heat haze
That was my middle school.
Let's go see.
Okay.
You used to wear those too?
Yeah.
Looks like middle schoolers from the country.
Jeez.
Hello.
He owns a tea shop in the neighborhood.
I see.
It sure is cold today.
You're right. It looks like it might snow.
My...
You must have left home very early to get here this early.
Sorry. We just suddenly decided to come.
That's right
I slept over at Onii-chan's house last night.
I see. You guys must get along very well.
Oh yeah. What's that?
Oh, that?
That's just for a little change of mood.
Oh.
Well, take your time.
Yeah.
Yes? Welcome. The usual?
Yes, please. Oh yes, the shampoo you gave me last week, it's so good...
Koshiro?
Yeah?
Do be careful.
I'm not a pro, so I'm not sure if I can fix it.
I think it's because a tile is cracked.
Could you at least try?
The leak is terrible.
I guess it can't be helped.
Man, it's freezing.
Is it fixed?
Probably... Actually, I don't know.
Eh, what? Which one?
That's because the kid next door...
Even so, this is so bad.
Ah! Don't look!
You really do look like a middle schooler from the country.
Just because there aren't many photos of you, Onii-chan. It's not fair!
Jeez...
Oh, yeah. I found these too.
Your collection of compositions from elementary school.
Ah, mom, not that.
"My dream is to become a beautician."
Jeez...
"That is because my mother is a beautician, so I want to take after her."
"I will also get married. I want lots of children."
"I will call my mother, father and brother and we'll all live together."
"Then I think it will be a lot of fun."
So she said.
It does seem like a lot of fun, though.
Your husband is going to have a tough time.
Umm...
Sorry for dropping in all of a sudden.
Umm... I'm sorry.
What are you saying?
You actually helped me out a lot.
At this rate, I would like you to come everyday.
Bye then...
Good night.
Be careful on your way back.
Should we commit lover's suicide?
I don't mind either way.
If you're okay with it, then I don't care which.
Don't say things like that.
I can't decide which...
I don't know... what to do... so easily...
Let's go home.
If you're not sure, then let's just go home for now.
I think it's fine to go home and then think it over.
Are you okay with that?
I'm fine.
That's why I said that I'm fine as long as I'm with you, Onii-chan.
And in the end, we're still alive.
Resignation
Unable to find the answer to...
What the right thing to do is...
Yo!
Hey.
You really did quit?
Yeah.
I really did quit.
What are you going to do from now on?
I haven't decided yet.
You sure do have absolutely no direction in your life.
If you're not able to do anything anymore, then you should just come back.
If I'm not able to do anything?
Do you really think it'll solve itself?
Sorry. I said that I wouldn't say anything anymore, didn't I?
Whatever happens... I can't wish you good luck, but...
Stay well.
Bye, now.
Let's go home, Nanoka!
Do you want to do some karaoke on the way?
Sorry, but there's somewhere I have to go.
Next time.
She doesn't hang out with us much anymore.
Yeah.
I bet it's a boyfriend.
I wonder.
Probably, most likely.
Yeah.
Do you want to follow her?
Let's follow her!
I want to see what kind of guy he is!
Nanoka's boyfriend!
But...
You guys peeped at my date!
Let's go!
What's wrong?
Let's not.
I'm kind of scared.
Kohinata Nanoka
Koshiro
Saeki Zenzou
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
The one thing I do know is...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Let's eat.
This moment...
Itadakimasu.
...is something that I don't want to let go of.
Do you have everything?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Suburban shopping malls are the trend of life.
But if this place is gone, then I think that many people will be sad.
Actually, there are more people in favor than in opposition.
There isn't that kind of an institution around here, so...
I think many of the residents felt that it was inconvenient.
Ah, is that so?
I feel that destroying the row of trees would be wasteful.
But I guess you can't do business with just sentiment.
Sorry, but you...
Why, you!
No!
Come here, you...
Stop it.
You little!
I'll go clean myself.
Yeah.
Here!
For me?
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Come here.
Hey...
Hurry, Onii-chan!
Amusement parks are...
Hmm?
...fun even if they aren't moving.
Is that so?
Wow!
How disappointing...
That it doesn't move.
I thought you said that it was fun even if it wasn't moving?
The ferris wheel is different.
You sure are hard to please.
But... it's better if it moves.
I bet it would be beautiful.
The town.
Yeah.
I wonder if we can't move it.
I was wondering if we can move it somehow.
How?
By praying.
Ehh...
You don't know unless you try.
But...
Come on, you try praying too.
It's impossible!
Don't give up so easily.
Come on, once more.
Ready...
We did it!
We did...
I can't believe it!
Once more, again!
Yeah...
Aren't we doing something stupid?
You're the one who started it!
Don't say that!
Ready? One... two...
Really... what are we doing?
Nanoka
Here.
Saeki
Let's come again!
Sure.
Every year, in the spring.
Yeah.
It's a promise!
I'm going home then.
Do you want to take a bath at my place first?
I'm fine like this.
I see...
Bye!
Ah!
Ah, no... It's nothing.
What?
It's nothing.
Later.
I love you.
I love you!
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a Dew frost
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.