hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
Gentle Breeze
I can’t sleep...
Why do I...
...keep thinking about her?
Now that I think about it,
when I was really little,
there were nights when I couldn’t fall asleep.
At times like that,
Mom would soothe me by patting my head.
That’s weird.
I swear it was somewhere in here.
That’s right.
When I was a little kid, without him...
What am I supposed to do about it?
You’re the one who left it there.
We’ll call the bus company first
thing tomorrow morning, all right?
My poor boy...
Just like Mom did for me back then,
I should do something nice for her.
Maybe then this strange feeling will go away.
That’s what I found myself thinking.
Am I really that childish?
Perhaps her innocence is what makes her seem childlike?
Or...
What do you want?!
How cute!
Is this yours, Onii-chan?
Don’t just come into my room like that!
How surprising!
You treasure such a cute teddy bear?
No, it’s not that I’m treasuring it.
Yes, you are!
You washed and cleaned him, right?
No, that wasn’t... what I...
But it’s not nice to dry him like this!
Right?
If you want it, I’ll give it to you.
But...
My mom made it for me when I was a kid.
It doesn’t really matter to me if you take it.
I’ll give it to you.
Wait a second!
Here!
This one’s mine.
Mom made one for me too.
You can have it.
I’ll keep this one,
so take care the other one, Onii-chan.
I don’t want this.
No! You need to take care of him!
Don’t bully him!
She’s definitely still just a kid...
...At least, that’s what I think.
Or what I’d like to think...
What? You just arrived at third period?
When I woke up, the morning show was over.
So I decided I’d just come in for afternoon classes.
You should’ve just taken the whole day off.
But you know,
being late was kind of lucky!
I saw this really cute guy on the train!
What’d he look like?
He was pretty tall,
with fair skin and straight, shiny hair.
He also had amazing eyelashes!
He must be a high school student, since he was wearing a school uniform!
Why was he on the train that late?
Yeah! That’s exactly the point!
The point?
I was so late, but he was on the same train car, on the same train, at the same time!
Don’t you think it’s fate?
Yeah, sounds like it!
Isn’t it? Isn’t it? I feel a romance coming on!
Romance...?
Loser buys drinks!
Fine, because I’m going to win.
Nanoka?
Was it?
Yeah. Thanks!
You’re a life saver.
Are you okay?
You don’t look so well.
I’m fine.
Marriage
Consulting
Huh?
Koshiro, you’re the day off tomorrow?
Yeah, it’s compensation for working overtime last week.
Isn’t Mr. Wakanae’s arranged marriage meeting tomorrow?
Is it?
Yeah, it is.
Shoot, I’d completely forgotten about it.
I’ll come in the afternoon.
It’s okay.
You can take the day off.
I’ll go to it for you.
That won’t work!
He’s extremely shy around strangers.
To keep him from getting nervous, we have to start from that meeting room,
then go to a nearby cafe, then go to a European restaurant—
How can I let you handle such a delicate job?
You’ve been acting very pensive recently.
See, there you go, getting lost in thought again.
Anyway, you should get some rest tomorrow.
Yeah...
That cute guy you were talking about earlier,
which school does he go to?
I wish I could’ve found that out...
I’ve never seen his uniform before.
Maybe it’s the all-boys school that started up last year.
But if he was on the same train as you today,
there’s a chance you’ll see him again, right?
I want to see what he looks like too!
What? What’s go—?
Shh! Shhh!
What should I do?
It’s that blonde guy?
Oh my god! Can I believe in fate?
He’s the guy from this morning?!
Hey, you think he’s good-looking too, right?
What should I do?
Wait a minute!
I want to take a better look at him!
Nanoka...
Hey, you saw that, right?!
That was Tamaki, right? He was kissing Tamaki, right?
Y-Yeah.
That girl! She said she wasn’t interested!
I’ll make her spill it all out tomorrow!
I’m home.
You...
Welcome home. You’re early today.
What’s wrong?
What’s that medicine for?
Oh, it’s nothing,
just a pain reliever.
I’m going to go lie down in my room, okay?
H-H-Hey, is Nanoka all r-r-right?
She probably stayed up too late last night.
Nanoka...
Please    knock
Nanoka
It looks like the beginning of the rainy season.
The Kantou area is covered by a low-pressure system.
There won’t be any rain from tonight till tomorrow morning,
but it will most likely rain tomorrow afternoon.
Please don’t forget to take an umbrella when you go out.
Next, tomorrow’s weather for each area in Tokyo.
It will be cloudy followed by rain in Tokyo City.
The probability of precipitation in the morning is 60%,
and in the afternoon it will be 70%.
Aren’t you hungry?
Where are you going at this hour?
A walk.
What are you saying?
You’re not feeling well, right?
I’m just having really bad menstrual cramps.
It’s the first time in three months?
Are you all right?
The doctor told me it’s common for girls my age.
I’m sorry for making you worry even though I’m not really sick.
It’s fine.
Do you want to go to the convenience store on the way back?
Are you all right? Don’t force yourself!
Onii-chan, you worry too much.
I’m fine.
Today...
I saw my friend kissing a guy.
I wonder if someday I’ll get to kiss someone.
I’m going to have you explain everything about yesterday!
There’s nothing to explain.
Where did you meet him?
In junior high. We went to the same cram school.
Cram school?!
That’s the kind of place I’d never go!
Ouch!
I said something weird last night...
Onii-chan is probably used to kissing.
He’s an adult.
When will I become an adult?
I wish I could find myself some good romance.
What?
Is that strange?
Not really.
Right?
Crap!
Shit...
It’ll probably stop soon.
When you’re in love, even boring things make your heart jump!
That’s what makes it really fun!
Yeah!
Oh no, it’s gotten worse.
Onii-cha—
Onii-chan!
I’m back.
Did you come to pick me up?
No way.
I was on my way to the store because I ran out of cigarettes.
It’s true! I only brought one umbrella too!
Yeah.
I know.
Are you all right?
Your stomach ache?
What are you smiling about?
Nothing.
Whatever.
Weirdo.
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
Our client’s scheduled marriage meeting completely slipped my mind.
Next episode:
Evening Shower
Koshiro's ex-girlfriend sees him with Nanoka... so he meets with her to explain.
But Koshiro gets very nervous about having a date... with his ex after such a long time.
I bullied a teddy bear by giving it a noogie.
I ogled her underwear that was hung out to dry.
I can't help it!
It's only natural if you're a man!
Innocent
Innocent. No punishment.