hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
Spring Blues
The town I was born in.
The house I was born in.
My father and older brother.
It’s like I just met them for the first time—
but they’re already very dear to me.
Good morning, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, wait up!
I’m home.
Welcome back, Onii-chan.
Isn’t this stew delicious?
Yeah.
My mother taught me how to make it.
Onii-chan!
Eh?
Let’s go to the amusement park again!
Somehow, everything looks like it’s sparkling.
A younger sister...?
Good morning, Onii-chan!
Umm...
What do you usually have for lunch?
I made you a boxed lunch today.
If it’s all right with you, will you take it?
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan!
Really? And then what?
He claimed it was anemia.
Is he that frail?
He’s been looking pretty pale lately.
I see.
I want to...
become...
closer to...
my brother.
You don’t get along with him?
It’s not that,
but being around him feels so awkward.
That’s just because he’s
twelve years older than you.
But still...
We are siblings after all.
The fire of envy has set my heart ablaze.
How delightfully lovely.
That idiot!
Well, I guess I’ll head home.
Good work.
You should hurry up and go home early too.
Isn’t your cute little sister waiting?
That’s precisely why I don’t want to.
Have her make you a meal full of love!
Just like she did with your lunch!
Shut up!
There’s nothing to worry about!
I’ll take care of your membership entrance!
Um, I’m not interested.
You are...
Glasses...
Glasses...?
Onii-chan!
You!
I came to visit.
So she says.
Why don’t we all go out and eat together?
Hurry up and finish your work.
Dad said he would be late today so we should go out and eat.
Onii-chan, what would you like to eat—
Hey, Koushiro!
Idiot! Why did you come all the way here?!
Because...
Listen, I don’t want you to ever come to my office again!
Understand?
Onii-chan,
did I...
Hey, Onii-chan—
Enough! Stop calling me “Onii-chan”!
Then...
Then what should I call you?
Hey!
That was my big chance to legally become acquainted with a high school girl.
He was such a jerk!
He went off to work early by himself.
Yesterday, weren’t you saying you wanted to be closer to him?
I’m so disappointed.
To be honest,
I want to have fun with with him and have him help me with homework.
It wasn’t supposed to be like this.
Aren’t most siblings like that?
All I do is fight with my older sister.
I didn’t expect him to be so mean!
I’m never going to call my brother “Onii-chan” again!
Now, now.
Hey, why don’t we go have some fun after school,
and really let out our feelings!
Okay?
Yeah!
Poor girl.
She visited you because she wanted to spend time with you.
Your behavior was uncalled-for, wasn’t it?
Shut up! I know that already.
Then what?
What do you not like about her?
It’s nothing.
It’s not like I dislike her.
When she’s in front of me,
I just feel like running away.
What’s wrong with you?
Did you snap after your girlfriend walked out?
I had forgotten...
I had forgotten about her... completely.
Damn it!
It’s so sweet!
This is so good!
Isn’t it, isn’t it?
Chocolate caramel ice cream is definitely the best!
Yeah!
Nanoka, you don’t really know the shops in this area yet, do you?
Let’s go shopping together next time.
I’ll show you around!
Yeah!
Hey, Futaba-chan!
What’s up?
You’re eating here again?
You sure love the ice cream here.
She went to the same junior high as me.
I’m Tamaki Youko from class four. Nice to meet you.
I’m Kohinata Nanoka. Nice to meet you, too.
Hey, I’m heading to a karaoke box with my friends.
Do you two want to join us?
I’m home.
What are you doing?
Nanoka called...
She said she’s going to be home late!
What?
She called, so what’re you worried about?
You idiot!
Right now, Nanoka could be surrounded by strange men trying to kidnap her!
If something like that were ever to happen...
I’d... I’d...
You’re overreacting.
Karaoke
Ah! I sang a lot!
It was so much fun!
I feel so refreshed.
I know, right?
It’s gotten kind of late, huh?
Will you be okay, Nanoka?
I called home just in case.
Let’s do this again some time!
Yeah!
I’ll see you tomorrow, then.
See you! Bye!
Try to make up with your brother.
This is the Saeki residence.
This is Nanoka.
Are you stupid?!
Why did you stay out this late?
Um, I mean...
Where are you right now?
At the public phone outside the park.
Why did you take that route?
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Don’t you know there are a lot of perverts in that area?
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Fine! I got it!
I was just calling to tell you I’m on my way home!
Bye!
Hey! Hello?
What’s with him?!
He’s so arrogant!
He was crying just the other day.
I know now.
That time,
I didn’t understand why he was crying,
but because he cried, I didn’t have to.
Even when I think about the guy I used to like,
I’m all right now.
But...
Why do I feel like this now?
Get on.
No.
Who do you think I came all the way out here for?
Hurry up and get on.
I didn’t ask you to come, Onii-chan!
It’s fine.
You can call me whatever you like.
Dad’s worried about you.
Let’s go home.
Ready?
Yeah.
Onii-chan?
What?
Nothing.
As for me,
I was getting irritated from still feeling uncomfortable.
She’s my younger sister.
So this is fine.
This is normal, and ordinary.
I continued pedaling as I tried to convince myself of that.
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
I do not intend to abuse my
position as a marriage consultant!
Next episode:
Gentle Breeze
They exchange teddy bears. Getting in a good mood.
But, Nanoka is acting strange, and it makes Koshiro nervous.
I just want to honestly and legally get to know some high school girls!
Hide his glasses
Hide his glasses as punishment!
Glasses!