hajimete no kimochi
I feel this way for the first time.
shonbori no mune ni
A ray of sunshine
sotto nagerareta hidamari ne
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
hitori aruiteta
Walking alone,
sora miageta toki
I looked up at the sky,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
and saw spring was near.
misetekureta
It showed me
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
like whirling petals.
sukininatte iino
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
Or...
tamerau kokoro ga
My hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
puts on the brakes.
kurushikute ikiga
It’s so painful,
tomarisou desu
I can’t breathe.
First Flower
It’s been a while since I’ve stopped caring about the changing of the seasons.
Please keep the
restrooms clean
Shirafuji.
Please keep the
restrooms clean
Shirafuji.
Please keep the
restrooms clean
Passengers headed to Manase,
please wait for the express train that arrives next.
How much meaning is there to the fact that it is spring right now?
I’ve fallen in love with someone else.
Oh... I see.
Tsubana. Tsubana.
Please wait until the train has come to a complete stop.
Excuse me, I’m getting off.
H-Hey... Excuse me.
Hey, you there!
Hey, student!
Yes?
Oh... Here.
Oh, no. I didn’t realize I’d dropped it.
Thank you very much.
You’re welcome.
Machida Marriage Consulting
That’s all I have about the next arranged marriage party.
If nobody has any questions, then I would like to end the meeting.
Yes!
Odagiri.
This party is restricted to members in their late twenties to early thirties.
However, I suggest we lower the age requirement,
and create a party comprised solely of teenage girls—
That’s all!
Good work, guys.
Let’s go eat!
Where do you want to go?
Didn’t a new restaurant open up in Kanami?
Really?
Koshiro.
Huh?
You’re sorting the membership data files in the back today.
Why?
That face... And that smell!
I can’t show that to our customers.
Reference Room
The toilet is
in the front.
I’m certain there’s a demand.
You think so?
From experience, men my age can only meet teenage girls illegally.
So, it’s just your demand.
I wonder if I’ll get a chance to meet a female high school student?
You just keep working.
I’m ho...me.
I wasn’t told about this!
Anyway, you’re going to be living with Nanoka starting tomorrow night.
Prepare yourself!
So suddenly...
I wanted you to meet Nanoka.
You remember her, don’t you?
Yes, I do.
I do remember her, though I don’t remember her face.
She’s a first-year in high school now.
Fifteen years old. She’s so cute!
Lots of students commute long-distance nowadays.
Her commute time will be reduced from two hours to one!
Isn’t it reasonable to let her stay here?
You’re not trying to get back together with Mom
just because your lover dumped you, are you?
That’s not how it is!
It’s not?
No!
She’s my daughter!
She’s family!
Your younger sister!
Living my carefree life with Dad,
I sometimes forget:
I have a mother and a sister who’s twelve years my junior.
Please introduce her to me!
What the hell are you thinking?
Why were you hiding something so important from me?!
I wasn’t really hiding it.
We simply don’t even know each other.
My parents are divorced.
Even though I’ve met my mom, who took custody of her, a few times,
I haven’t seen my sister at all.
You have a customer!
Machida Marriage Consulting
Sorry to keep you waiting.
So...
What kind of man are you interested in?
Don’t be mad.
I’m sorry for bothering you at work.
It’s all right.
I’m on lunch break anyway.
I came to get the keys to my place back.
I felt it would be more appropriate to do this during the day.
Just a minute.
Well, then.
Yeah.
You’re really letting me go without a fuss.
Sorry.
But...
You just accepted it so easily.
I just thought,
“Oh, I didn’t mean that much to to you”.
Koshiro, have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
What should I have done, then?
There are three events planned to happen during the party,
so we’d like the food to be served at the right times.
Next, concerning the audio equipment...
Thank you for your business.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Sakuragaoka Amusement Park
Here. These are for the place next door.
Oh, thank you very much.  Don’t mind if I do.
What do I say to a woman who says she’s in love with someone else?
What should I have done?
What a great view.
Sakuragaoka
This place kind of hurts for a bachelor.
Amusement Park
Sakuragaoka
So you broke up?
Amusement Park
Sakuragaoka
Yeah.
Amusement Park
Sakuragaoka
You’re so cool about it.
Amusement Park
Sakuragaoka
That’s what she disliked about me.
Amusement Park
Here, I’ll give these to you.
I don’t need them.
Why don’t you try asking the girl you just broke up with?
Maybe you two will get back together.
Who the hell’d want to get back together with—
Ah! Hello.
Do you remember me?
Yesterday morning.
Yeah, I remember!
I remember you.
Ah, I’m glad.
Such a naughty boy!
Asking out high school girls?
That’s not how it is!
Thank you for yesterday.
I’m sorry for interrupting your date.
That’s wrong too!
Hey!
Well...
Yes?
Here.
Please take these.
Idiot.
Umm...
This is perfect. I was waiting to meet someone,
but I arrived too early and needed to kill time.
Meet someone?
Yes. My father.
Hey, what would you like to ride?
Are you all right?
What the hell am I doing?
Here.
Wow! Thank you very much.
I’m sorry.
It must be boring to be with me.
Not at all.
Don’t you have a boyfriend?
I just got rejected by someone.
Wow! It’s so beautiful!
This...
I received this during my junior high graduation...
From the person I liked.
But it wasn’t his second button.
In Japan, it is a tradition upon graduation to give the second button from your school uniform to the girl you like.
I liked him ever since I was a first-year.
He wasn’t really handsome or anything,
but I really liked him.
I gathered up all my courage and confessed to him, but...
He said he’s going out with a junior.
I didn’t know about it at all.
If the window could be opened,
I would throw it away from here.
What a shame.
Don’t say you’ll throw it away.
You still like him, don’t you?
So don’t say that you’ll throw it away.
But...
I have to forget about him.
He has someone that he’s going out with.
We go to different schools now.
I can’t even see him anymore.
So why?
Why would you say that?
You’re so straightforward.
How is it...
How can you love someone so frankly and honestly?
I...
I just got dumped too.
Well, it’s rather different than your situation.
My feelings totally cooled off.
I don’t really know if I ever even loved her.
But...
That’s why...
You should definitely treasure...
those heartfelt emotions.
Huh?
Why am I...?
I was so surprised.
The cherry blossoms.
Since I got rejected, I’ve been walking with my head down,
so I didn’t notice the cherry blossoms at all.
When you stopped me at the train station,
I noticed them for the first time.
I was really surprised!
The petals were falling like snow,
and for a moment I felt like I was in a different world.
It was the same for me.
Where is this...
this place that I’ve always been?
Is it possible for me to stay here forever?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Umm...
No, it’s nothing.
Well, I have to...
Hey!
Sorry I’m late.
Dad!
Father?
Huh?!
Oh, you’re here too, Koshiro?
It’s been so long since you siblings have gotten together.
Did you two recognize each other right away?
Hey, what’s wrong with the two of you? Let’s go!
Hey...!
What should we have for dinner?
Nanoka, what do you want?
Wait...
Dad...
Brother?
That’s right.
I have...
A little sister.
yasashii yume ga
A gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satte yuku
that touches you, then leaves.
chiisana potto ni wa
In the small pot
daisuki na kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly.
ii kaori nosete
They carry a sweet scent,
itsumo matteita
always waiting,
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment.
futari dakara wakaru koto
We understand each other
kotoba ja nakute
without words.
hohoemu dake negau dake
We just smile and hope
shizuka na sora he
to the peaceful sky.
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
shizuka na sora de
to the peaceful sky.
AN EPIC SERIES PREVIEW
CHIDORI'S JUDGEMENT
The girl who dumped me came to my office, so I was kind of apprehensive.
Next episode:
Spring Blues
Nanoka, who is Koshiro's sister, starts to live with him.
Nanoka calls him "big brother", and Koshiro gets into a quandary.
I went on a date with a girl, not knowing she was my younger sister.
Even though I’m this old, I cried in front of a high school student.
Is that enough?!
Wrap him up and throw him in the river
Wrap him up and throw him in the river as punishment!
Why?!